Hello, welcome once again to the Shaheed Diwas channel.
Today in this video
I will tell you about the
claim process of ICICI Lombard Health Insurance. I will
tell you about that in this video today. For this, first of all
you have to go to Google and type it as
you can see on the screen, ICICI
Lombard Reimbursement from ICICI
Lombard Improvement Form. As soon as you type it,
a form will appear in front of you. Now you
can see it on the screen, it will appear in
front of you and you can download the form from such a website,
ICICI Lombard
Hospitalization.
Now you will click here. If we click on it, then
see, you can download it from here.
First of all, you have to
download it. Okay, now
after downloading, there are total four parts in this form.
First, I will add the text A so that
you can see it more clearly. After that, the
second part is Part B
and the third part is Text Mark
and the fourth part is Water Deer
that this is Part O
but remember one thing and
Applicable for Dead Skin, it is written here, Party
Only for Retail Public Individual  Customer
is planning better than OLX ₹2
If Airtel digital customer is more than 1 lakh
then they have to fill it, otherwise
they do not have to fill it, if it is less than 1 lakh
then it is fine 48 text text text text
What other forms do you have to fill, you
only have to fill the declaration in the party, only the
verification will come
later, applicable in policy
Scorpio price details
available in, price policy copy available in this
chart summary only relationship relation,
okay, all this thing you have to do in the party again,
okay or what to fill, everything is given in the form,
now see, who will fill the party from,
it is also written, which form, who will fill it,
see you also have to fill the field
on its project, it is written, there is a field
part which has to be clicked, which is
written again, this has to be filled, by insured
relative means the one in
whose name the insurance policies health
insurance policy, either that party will fill it
or any relative of his family will fill it,
okay now this is part 1  Why
is it requested? Why is it necessary to do it? The
reason for this is required to do it.
See, how to
trade policy and the details of
insult daily bench, politician and other
details. This party
form has to be filled and this will be filled
by informed and in sodium zinc, the
person in whose name the policy is issued will call or
one of their relatives.
What do you have to fill in the party form, it is written here.
Who will fill in the form, it was also written in the text,
why is it necessary to do the party again,
this is also written. After this, let's
move forward, see in the text, we have to
fill in the hospital details, we have to fill in the doctor details, we have to
click on this, we have to
fill in the treatment and procedure details, so in the
text, which type of Yagya is also given,
in that field, the hospital fabric painting
doctor means the doctor who has done the treatment, then he
can do it, or the hospital or
nursing, which is the one who can do the fruit, Part
B A and the second, why is it necessary to do it quickly,
Part B B is written, track the
hospital details and treatment details
related to the patient admission, that is  To track the
hospital details and
treatment details of the patient, the
fifth tip has to be done
and this Tilak will be ₹15. If the hospital is treating the patient, then the
public shooting boxer means the doctor is doing the
treatment, then he can do it or the
hospital can decide the nursing home,
after that it will go to Parts E Want C,
in one section C see what details
you have to click on, patient name, policy
number, card number, group number, company name, in this
way the hint depression has to be folded in the part
and Parts E Can Help,
this is also written because the field
by episode, episode daily, in whose name the
policy is on this side, the person will do this part,
why is it necessary to do this, the
reason for this is given and electronic
fund transfer to the bank account, that is, to
transfer the plan money,
if the claim is settled, then the money will be
transferred to the bank,
this test is being taken on it, it
is necessary to fill the part form and more than this, as
I have given this section, this section is only for those
who are retail and diesel customers and the amount is
more than 1 lakh, if it is clear then the part  You have to
click if there is no need to fill the white part E, if it is
clear if you want to wish someone with more than 1 lakh birthday
what not to do in the party patient
name policy number card number and liquid this
number group company name is Raj Yoga have to be recited
and party can be done
if it has to be done soon in
whose name the policy is, he should recite it
more than 1 lakh and the second thing is that it is
necessary to do what is it being done
what is the reason for this the reason
is written
in the TRP of Parathas IRDA Mandate for Play it
is necessary to fill the rule as you must be knowing that
according to whatever speed it does it is
necessary to do it
president ji president ji and now
after this you must have understood all these things that
which training you have to click the form will come
see
that now tell me the important thing and what
documents you have to take see it is written
documents submitted
documents submitted what
documents you have to submit the
list of the rocks that you have to submit is
also given plane from every field
discharge summary day care summary liner
hospital bill payment  You have to submit receipt,
investigation report, pharmacy bill,
share amount details or everything.
After filling up the application form, now see which originals you have to
submit, which xeroxes i.e.
photocopies have to be submitted, but
see the type of document, the one which will be original,
sorry, it is written, see, like the
first one is plain from every field claim
form, you have to submit it and this is
written, you have to click on original, okay, similarly,
then we will go ahead, then there
is discharge summary, day care
summary, you have to submit this also, apart from this,
you have to pay attention to the final hospital bill also, you have to
submit many documents in this way
and you have to give photocopies of some of the documents below,
like you have to give this, doctor's
caption is written, doctor's training and you will
see in front of it, doctor's prescription, you have to give photocopy of it as well, that is, you have to give photocopy of the same in the same way,
something like this, the second document,
you have to give photocopy of it,
consultant paper,
consultation paper, sorry,
you have to give photocopy of consultation paper also, in this way you have to give some
documents  You have to put it and give some
photocopies and
this is the complete list of documents submitted,
what all documents will you need,
starting from serial number 1 to serial number 1,
okay, you have given the payment details till serial number 13,
you have to search all these documents, some documents are
original, some documents you just have to submit,
okay, what are the parts of the sperm, what do you have to
fill,
who can fill, why, then you have to do it
and its box will be like I have shown,
now this main from your form
is very simple in this form, click the
text written like party because the field by
installed daily, that the person whose name is the brain, in
whose name he
will seal it, if he is not able to do it then
his family, some relative will seal it,
in this simply you have to click
everything, it is written name of a saint,
card number, gender gender information, voice mail has to be done, in
this way the text by part
seal and party or if applicable then okay,
party if you are only then you have to do it  So in
this way, after clicking on all these forms, you will
attach all the required documents.
After attaching them, you have to
submit it to the branch
from which your insurance policy has been done, that is, the
branch from which your health insurance
policy has been done, you have to go and submit it to that branch.
After this, it takes
some time for the entire process to be completed, it takes around
a month. Well,
within that time, if your play gets
settled, then you will get the money.
Friends, that's all for today. If you liked the video, then
like it and if you
like my channel, then please subscribe to the channel and
press the bell icon.
Thank you, thank you Ajay.